O.k., we're talking about motorcycle safety and safety equipment and different options that you have.
Let's get a little more in depth with you on safety equipment and your options.
These are what is called a racing suit.
They're for advanced riders.
They are a full race suit, two piece race suit actually.
You have different options but they are strictly leather.
We have a perforated leather over here for you to show you and a full leather.
They do zip at the waist.
They do have your full body armor on them.
And that is from wrist to above elbow and from below elbow to shoulder and a full back plate with full leg plate, full knee part on them which means that you have your knee armor.
They are very very, very very strictly regimented track race safety material.
I brought them out just because I thought they'd be fun for you to look at and then give you a little bit more information on what you are looking at when it comes to safety gear and what you can look for to buy when you're ready for the track.